'RIO JIHAN

Jakarta (City), Indonesia, Indonesia +62 8963 711 6885 • Rlojihan01.github.io • riojihan0110@gmail.com

Personal statement

Hello, my name is Rio Jihan, I am 19 years old, I come from Indonesia, my hobbies are drawing and sports such as football and martial arts, but I was also active in several fields when I was in junior high school, such as participating in martial arts competitions, taking part in scout activities, joining futsal competition. Apart from that, I also like drawing, but I draw according to my heart, sometimes I draw something abstract, ugly and sometimes beautiful. My dream is to be a person who can make my family proud and elevate my parents.

Work Experience

computer store, ilda computer

06/2023 - Present

Responsibilities & Achievements

I work serving buyers, creating websites, delivering goods to the main shop, cleaning the shop

apprenticeship, PT DIGITAL UNIVERSAL INTERNASIONAL TRANSFER

09/2022 - 12/2022

Responsibilities & Achievements

There I also studied more deeply about web design and web development, the same as in the previous place because this was an internship program from school

Apprenticeship, PT INOVINDO DIGITAL MEDIA

07/2022 - 09/2022

Responsibilities & Achievements

There I learned more about full stack web development which was divided into teams and I made wireframes, UI design and some of the displays.

wedding decoration, woodqueen

06/2020 - 05/2023

Responsibilities & Achievements

I work as a wedding decoration, such as arranging flowers, table chairs, making an empty room beautiful for a husband and wife

Qualifications

progate

2020

completion certificate html & css (Other)

progate

2020

completion certificate java script (Other)

PT. Digital Universal Internasional Transfer

2022

Certificate Of Internship program (Other)

ditekindo & BNSP

2022

CERTIFICATE OF APPRECIATION SEO-Perspektif (Other)

progate

2020 - 2020

completion certificate java script

Education

SMK PERTIWI KUNINGAN

Software Engineering (2022 – 2023)

MTs PUI CILIMUS

(2017 - 2020)

MTs PUI CILIMUS

(2011 - 2017)